corexchange.com 2012-12-26

# Dallas Managed Network Solutions, Colocation Hosting and Internet Access

CoreXchange has created this privacy policy based on its commitment to protect your online privacy and appropriately manage your personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy sets out the practices that CoreXchange engages in with respect to the gathering and dissemination of your personal information if you are either an existing customer or simply a person who is accessing our web site. CoreXchange uses your Personal Information in order to personalize your experience on our web site and also to be able to selectively send you communications that may be of interest to you, either electronically or otherwise. CoreXchange gathers this information for internal use only. We utilize industry best practices in maintaining the security of such information and require that all of our employees enter into.

###  **Cookies**

Some of the pages on our web site may use "cookies," which are small pieces of text that a web site computer places in your computer's hard drive. We use cookies for the following reasons:

  * To enable us to customize content or advertising to match your interests

  * To avoid showing repeated advertising to visitors

  * To compile aggregate and anonymous statistics to use in improving the performance and features of our web site

  * To count the number of anonymous users on our web site

  * To help us recognize returning visitors as unique visitors, by number only, to our web site

###  **Server Log Information**

We also collect information to analyze usage patterns and properly administer the web site and our associated web servers. Such information may include your Internet Protocol address, your usage patterns on our web site, the state or country from which you accessed our site.

###  **Personal Information**

On some pages within our site, you may enter personal information to create or modify service orders, participate in surveys or forums, or request personalized content. While purchasing services on our site, you may be asked to supply information about your financial institution or your credit card. We use such information only to charge and bill you for services so purchased and may provide information to your credit card provider if you purchase services by credit card. We may ask you to provide your name, mailing address, phone numbers, e-mail address, and other types of unique identifiers for other types of registrations. We may then contact you with information about CoreXchange's services. We may store and encrypt any of the aforesaid information for logging purposes, when required by any law or regulation.

###  **User Consent**

By using this web site, you consent to the terms of CoreXchange’s Privacy Policy and to our use and processing of your personal information, as described above, for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. CorexChange reserves the right to change the terms of its Privacy Policy at any time. If we do change this privacy policy, we will post the changes on this web site. We encourage you to review this privacy policy each time you visit our web site to make sure you understand our current policy on collecting and using information collected through our web site.
